Finding aid for Mike Wallace CBS/60 Minutes Papers, 1922-2007
Bentley Historical Library
- Correspondence
  - 1999-2008 (Box 175)
    (includes publicity photographs of Wallace and the cast of 60 Minutes, and miscellaneous other photographs)
- *Personal
  - Project and interview requests, 2005-2007 (Box 175)
  - Washington Speakers Bureau, 2004-2007 (Box 175)
  - FDR: Four Freedoms Medal, 2006 (Box 175)
  - Events and invitations, 2005-2008 (Box 175)
  - Depression and Bipolar Support Alliance, 2006 (Box 175)
  - Depression Essays, Speeches, PSAs, 2006 (Box 175)
  - Printed material on depression and mental illness, 2006 (Box 175)
  - "Between You and Me" (Box 176)
    - Book tour and DVD, 2005 (Box 176)
    - Reviews, articles, and correspondence, 2005 (Box 176)
    - List of book party invitees, 2005 (Box 176)
    - Photo album of book tour, 2005 (Box 176)
  - News release on deposit of archives at Bentley Historical Library, 2006 (Box 176)
- Miscellaneous CBS News
  - Republican National Convention, 1964 (Box 176)
    (includes CBS News Correspondence Notebook, lists of contact information, notes, and ephemera)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, correspondence, studio copy, and notes (Box 176)
  - National Press Club certificate of appreciation, 1997 (Box 176)
  - Photographs (Box 176)
    (includes publicity photos and photos of Wallace with Bill Clinton, Yasser Arafat, Fidel Castro, Walter Cronkite, Aldous Huxley, Henry Cabot Lodge, and others)
  - Log of 60 Minutes program segments (Box 176)
Related Material
A separate collection of Mike Wallace Papers at the Bentley Historical Library covers Wallace's television and newspaper career in the years 1956 to 1963. It includes personal and professional correspondence, administrative files, transcripts and outlines of shows, research material, unedited texts of interviews, and other materials related to Night Beat New York Post Column, Newsmaker Productions, Mike Wallace Interview Survival And Freedom Ben Hecht Show WNTA Mike Wallace Interview, and photographs.
The Harry Ransom Center at the University of Texas at Austin houses Mike Wallace Interview audio/visual recordings and transcripts of 65 interviews from 1957 and 1958 as well as related materials, including his prepared questions, research material, and correspondence. For more information about the Mike Wallace Interview collection and to access the interviews held by the Harry Ransom Center at the University of Texas at Austin, go to http://www.hrc.utexas.edu/collections/film/holdings/wallace/